{
    "id": "527738a504314285b25b792bf1355c16",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is ................................ his seventeenth year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ...................................... eighteen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "above",
                "over",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... my opinion it is wrong.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In",
                "With",
                "On"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Our house is built .................................... bricks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He went ......................................... the building.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "behind",
                "back",
                "beneath"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was prevented ................................... coming.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a match ..................................... Team A and Team B.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "among",
                "for",
                "between"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a fight ................................... John and Peter yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among",
                "against"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The First World War was fought ................................. 1914 and",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "during",
                "between"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked ..................................... a rise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyday he walks ten miles ................................... foot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I shall inform them ........................................ this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}